Drop requires JavaScript to work, but it is disabled in your web browser.  
Here are the [instructions on how to enable JavaScript in your web browser](https://www.enable-javascript.com/).

[Click to view our Accessibility Statement or contact us with accessibility-related questions](https://drop.com/accessibility)

[Balrog and Mithrandir Artisan Keycap

Type with fire and Maiar.

Shop Now

_keyboard\_arrow\_right_](https://drop.com/buy/drop-the-lord-of-the-rings-balrog-vs-gandolf-artisan-keycap-and-spacebar)

Free Standard Shipping in the US on orders over $99

Free Standard Shipping in the US on orders over $99

_shopping\_cart_

SIGN UP

SHOP

Mechanical Keyboards

Audiophile

Battlestations

new

Collections

More Ways to Shop

**PRIVACY POLICY**
==================

Introduction
------------

This Privacy Policy explains who we are, how we collect, share, and use Personal Data about you, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

**ACCESSING OR USING OUR SERVICE INDICATES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

### What Does Corsair Do?

Corsair is one of the world's leading providers of hardware, software, and services to enable gamers and streamers. With decades of experience in computer and video technology, Corsair offers a complete range of products to equip gamers, content creators, enthusiasts, and e-sports athletes to play at the highest levels of performance and experience and to produce professional content for worldwide audiences.

For more information about Corsair, please see the “About Us” section of our website at [www.corsair.com/about](https://drop.com/www.corsair.com/about).

### Privacy Policy Overview

Please read this Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. In this Privacy Policy, “**Corsair**,” “**we**,” “**us**,” and “**our”** refer collectively to Corsair Memory Inc., and its family of brands (including Corsair, Elgato, Gamer Sensei, Drop.com, Origin PC, and SCUF, as well as any of our current or future brands, subsidiaries, or affiliates “Affiliates”). This Privacy Policy may use terms defined in Corsair’s Terms of Use (“**Terms of Use**”). This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Data processed in connection with our “**Service**” which includes the following (without limitation):

1. Our “**Sites**” (including any mobile versions and subdomains):

* Corsair.com
* Elgato.com
* SCUFGaming.com
* OriginPC.com
* Gamersensei.com
* Drop.com
* Other domain names we may operate from time to time  

2. Our mobile applications (“**Apps**”), internet-connected hardware (“**Products**”), or internet-enabled software (collectively, “**Software**”), including (without limitation):

* Epocam
* iCUE
* WaveLink
* Elgato Control Center
* Elgato Screen Link
* Elgato Streamdeck
* Elgato Streamdeck Mobile
* Elgato Game Capture
* Elgato Camera Hub  

3. Our “**Platforms**” including:

* Elgato Marketplace
* Gamer Sensei  

4. Our products/services or advertisements provided on or through third party sites/services (e.g. advertisements delivered by third parties and data we collect through promotions on third party sites), or via social media (e.g. when we correspond with you via social media, when we access information provided by social media platforms in relation to our pages on those platforms, and when you reference or interact with our posts on social media).
    
5. Our offline services, for example, when we interact with customers at a conference, trade show, event, or over the phone, and our support services (e.g. when you contact us through online form or chat).
    
6. Our Services may include YouTube API Services. By accessing or using our Services that include YouTube API Services, You agree to [YouTube's Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) and [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy). For the YouTube application, you can revoke YouTube application’s access to your data via the [Google security settings page](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions).

Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new products , services, or features of our Service will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

In addition to this Privacy Policy, we provide additional information regarding the collection and use of Personal Data through specific products and services in our [Supplemental Privacy Notices](https://www.corsair.com/us/en/s/privacy-policy#other-supplemental-privacy-notices). Our Supplemental Privacy Notices are incorporated into this Privacy Policy and will control to the extent relevant to your activities and to the extent of any conflict with this Privacy Policy.

Finally, we provide specific information for users in certain locations. Click the following links to learn more:

This Privacy Policy only covers how Corsair processes Personal Data as part of our Service. Corsair’s Privacy Policy does not apply to third parties. We encourage you to read third party privacy policies and understand your privacy rights before interacting with them.

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices, accessible via the headings below, and contact us if you have any questions. To exercise your rights in Personal Data, contact us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com)

Navigation
----------

1. [What is Personal Data at Corsair?](#what-is-personal-data-at-corsair)
2. [Personal Data Corsair Collects](#personal-data-corsair-collects)
3. [How We Process Personal Data](#how-we-process-personal-data)
4. [Business and Commercial Purposes of Processing](#business-and-commercial-purposes-of-processing)
5. [Your Privacy Rights and Choices](#your-privacy-rights--choices)
6. [Data Retention](#data-retention)
7. [Corsair’s Sharing of Personal Data](#corsairs-sharing-of-personal-data)
8. [Protection of Data at Corsair](#protection-of-data-at-corsair)
9. [Transfer of Personal Data Between Countries](#transfer-of-personal-data-between-countries)
10. [Children](#children)
11. [Privacy Questions](#privacy-questions)
12. [Changes and Updates to our Privacy Policy](#changes-and-updates-to-our-privacy-policy)
13. [How to Contact Us](#how-to-contact-us)
14. [Supplemental Information for Users in the EEA/UK/Switzerland](#supplemental-information-for-users-in-the-eeaukswitzerland)
15. [Supplemental Information for Nevada Residents](#supplemental-information-for-nevada-residents)
16. [Supplemental Information for California Residents](#supplemental-information-for-california-residents)
17. [Other Supplemental Privacy Notices](#other-supplemental-privacy-notices)

WHAT IS PERSONAL DATA AT CORSAIR?
---------------------------------

“**Personal Data**” refers to data that relates, or that is linked or linkable, to an identified or identifiable individual or household. Personal Data includes data that directly identifies you — such as your name — as well as data that does not directly identify you, but that can reasonably be used to identify you — such as the serial number of your device.

PERSONAL DATA CORSAIR COLLECTS
------------------------------

The Personal Data Corsair collects depends on how you interact with Corsair and Corsair’s Affiliates. When you use our Service, we collect the following categories of Personal Data:

* **Identity Data**. Your name, Corsair account ID and related account details, including email address, devices and services registrations, account status, age, and geographic location.
* **Device/Network Data**. Data from which your device could be identified, such as device serial number or unique ID, or information about your device, such as software version. We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our Service, including the pages accessed and links clicked, IP address, as well as data from cookies or pixel tags that may be used to identify your device or behavior. This information may also include hardware IDs or information about our Products.
* **Contact Data**. Data such as email address, physical address, phone number, or other contact information.
* **Payment Data**. Data about your billing address and method of payment, such as credit, debit, or other payment card information. We keep your payment information until the warranty period on your purchased product expires.
* **Transaction Data**. Data about purchases of Corsair products and services or transactions facilitated by Corsair, including purchases made through our Service.
* **Audio/Visual Data**. Recordings and images collected through our Service, such as audio files, video recordings, and the like.
* **Usage Data**. Data about your activity on and use of our Hardware and Service, such as site and app performance data, browsing metadata; device and software interactions; user navigation flows; clickstream data; Software and device crash data, performance and other diagnostic data; and other device connectivity data.
* **Inference Data** – We may make inferences from Personal Data to create a profile, e.g. individual predispositions, behavior, and attitudes.
* **Location Data**. Personal Data relating to your geographic location, such as information collected from your device’s GPS, or location information you voluntarily provide to us.
* **Government ID Data**. In certain jurisdictions, we may ask for a government-issued ID in limited circumstances for the purpose of extending credit, verifying your identity, tax/income reporting, or complying with law.
* **User Content**. Information such as unstructured/free-form data that may include any category of Personal Data, e.g. data that you give us in free text fields such as comment boxes, Personal Data you provide when you complete forms on our Service, or answers you provide when you participate in sweepstakes, contests, and surveys.

Certain Personal Data is necessary for us to complete transactions and otherwise provide our Service, so if you choose not to provide Personal Data, we may not be able to provide our Service to you or respond to requests you may have.

### Sources of Personal Data

We collect Personal Data in various ways, which vary depending on the context in which we process that Personal Data:

* **Data you provide to us**. You may provide us or service providers/partners with Personal Data directly, for example, as part of account registration or when you provide information through the Service.
* **Automatic Collection**. We (or third parties operating on our behalf) may collect certain Personal Data automatically, for example, Device/Network Data is typically collected automatically through the use of cookies and similar technologies used on our Service.
* **Third Parties**. We may receive Personal Data from third parties with whom we have a relationship. For example, we may receive certain Personal Data from social media companies or data aggregators.
* **Inferred Data**. We may create Personal Data relating to inferences drawn from Personal Data we process in order to create a profile about you, or generate information relating to your predispositions, behavior, and attitudes.

HOW WE PROCESS PERSONAL DATA
----------------------------

We generally process your Personal Data in connection with the following activities and purposes, as well as for the general purposes described below.

### Account Registration

When you create an account on our Service, we process certain Personal Data, which typically includes Identity Data, Device/Network Data, Contact Data, and if you choose to provide it, Location Data. Similarly, if you use single sign-on services, we may receive this Personal Data from the provider of the single sign-on service, and we may associate this information with your Corsair account or specific Affiliate account, as appropriate. Please note – Affiliate accounts may be associated with Corsair accounts if we have information to link those accounts, and we may allow single sign-on for Affiliate accounts using your Corsair account. However, note that if you create an account using a third party single sign on, your account may not be automatically linked with your Corsair account.

We process this Personal Data primarily to create, maintain, and provide you with important information about your account, and provide the features and services you request. Additionally, we use the Transaction Data, Identity Data, and Contact Data as necessary to complete and provide you with important information regarding any related subscriptions. We process Payment Data only as necessary to process any purchases or subscription transactions that you request.

We may create certain Inference Data from your account data, or associate Inference Data with your account. We may use such Personal Data for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### When you make a Purchase or Conduct Another Transaction through our Service

We generally process Identity Data, Payment Data, Transaction Data and Contact Data when you engage in a purchase transaction, or subscription payment/renewal. Our Service may allow you to pay using third-party payment service providers (such as Venmo, Stripe, PayPal or Square). If you use a third-party payment processor where you have an account, your Personal Data will be processed by the third party as set forth in the third party’s privacy policy. We may receive your Contact Data, Identity Data and Transaction Data from the third party, in which case, such Personal Data will be processed as set forth in this section.

We process this Personal Data as necessary to perform or initiate a contract with you, process your order and payment, and carry out fulfillment and delivery. In addition, we may also collect or create Device/Network Data and Inference Data based on your transaction. Payment Data, together with other data we collect in this context is used as necessary in connection with our business purposes and may be used for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, each as described below.

We may also disclose your Personal Data to third-party service providers that carry out security and anti-fraud checks on the purchase transaction on our Service. The disclosure of Personal Data may be based on our legitimate interest in preventing fraudulent online transactions on the legal basis applicable in your country of residence.

### When you Access or Use our Service

When you use our Service, we automatically collect and process Device/Network Data and Usage Data. We process these data as necessary to initiate or fulfill your requests for certain features or functions through our Service, such as keeping you logged in, delivering pages, logging activities for security purposes, etc. In addition, we may also collect and process Contact Data, Identity Data, and Inference Data that we collect, create, and/or receive (including through the use of cookies and similar technologies, subject to any necessary consents required under applicable law). For more information, please visit our Cookies and Similar Technologies page [here](https://drop.com/privacy/cookies).

We may also process Identity Data, Contact Data, and User Content if you interact with or identify us, or relevant teams, sponsors, or other partners on social media platforms. Further, with your consent where required by law, we may process Location Data or Audio/Visual Data.

We process this data, together with Inference Data, and Device Data to improve our products and Service, to allow you to use certain interactive aspects of our Service, to allow you to participate in features or events, and in connection with other features that require the use of such data. Further, we may process Personal Data collected from your use of our Service for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### When you Use our Software or Certain Products

We collect certain Personal Data when you use our Software and certain products. For example, we may process Identity Data, Device/Network Data, Usage Data, or Audio/Visual Data relating to you and the relevant product or Software you are using. We may also create Inference Data derived from information collected through your use of our products/Software.

We generally use this information as you request, or in accordance with our legitimate business interests (or subject to any necessary consents), for certain telemetry, bug fixing, crash reporting, and similar logs and metrics relating to the performance and operation of the Software or Hardware. We may also process Personal Data collected via our products and Software for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

Please see our [Corsair Supplemental Privacy Notices](https://www.corsair.com/us/en/s/privacy-policy#other-supplemental-privacy-notices) for more information regarding the processing of Personal Data via specific Corsair products or Services.

### Email and SMS Campaigns

If you enroll in email or text message (SMS) marketing campaigns or if you engage in a transaction that allows us to enroll you in such campaigns (e.g. when you make a purchase, in certain jurisdictions) we may collect Identity Data and Contact Data, such as an email or phone number. We may also collect Device/Network Data and Contact Data so that we can determine whether you have opened an email or otherwise interacted with our communications, and we may generate Inference Data based on these interactions.

We will process these data as necessary to send you marketing and promotional communications for Corsair products and services, or those of our Affiliates, unless otherwise limited at the time you enroll. We process Personal Data collected for email/SMS campaigns for Commercial Purposes, including to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### Cookies and Other Technologies

The Service may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us to better understand customer behavior including for security and fraud prevention purposes, tell us which parts of our websites people have visited, facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches, and help us improve our marketing and advertising efforts.

As part of such processing, we (or our service providers) typically process Identity Data, Device/Network Data, Usage Data, Transaction Data, and Inference Data. Further, we may process such Personal Data for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below. For details regarding the data we collect, how we process and share that data, and your choices, please review our Cookies and Similar Technologies page [here](https://drop.com/privacy/cookies) or you may change your preferences using our Cookies Settings (here).

Note: Some of these technologies can be used by us and/or our third-party partners to identify you across platforms, devices, sites, and services. If you prefer that Corsair not use certain cookies, we may provide you with the means to disable their use (e.g. via our Cookie Settings) or you may disable cookies via your browser settings menu. Certain features of the Service may not be available or your experience may be impaired if you do not allow the use of certain cookies and similar technologies. At this time, we do not respond to browser “do-not-track” requests.

### Social Media Promoters

We may work with certain individuals that promote Corsair products (“Promoter”). We may track information relating to such Promoters, such as Device/Network Data, Identity Data, Contact Data, Inference Data, and Transaction Data relating to promotional communications, purchase conversations, and related metrics.

We process this Personal Data to establish and manage the Promoter relationship and assess performance, as well as for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

Please note – Certain Promoters may be active on third-party platforms, including social media platforms. We do not control the processing of Personal Data by such parties. Please review the privacy policies of the social media platforms for more information.

### When you Enter a Contest or other Promotion

We collect and process Identity Data, Contact Data, and in some cases, User Content, Transaction Data, Device/Network Data, and Inference Data when you participate in a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion. In some cases, service providers, third party providers, and social media platforms may collect and process this Personal Data on our behalf. Some third-party providers and social media platforms may also collect Personal Data and share it with us, or use it for their own purposes, as set forth in the applicable third party privacy policies.

We process this Personal Data as necessary to process your request to enter a contest or take part in a promotion, to notify you if you have won, to process delivery of a prize, or to further other related purposes. We also process such Personal Data in connection with our legitimate business interests, such as verifying your identity for authentication and security purposes and helping us to prevent fraud. Where allowed by applicable law, we may use this Personal Data for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

If you win a contest/sweepstakes, we may publicly post some of your Personal Data on our website (such as on a winners’ page). Where required by law, your Personal Data will not be posted without your consent.

Please note – certain promotions may be offered by third parties, including social media platforms. We do not control the processing of Personal Data by such third parties. Please review the privacy policies of the social media platforms for more information.

### Affiliate Relationships

If you would like to register to be an affiliate promoting Corsair products, you may be required to register with a third-party partner who will manage the affiliate relationship. We may receive certain Identity Data and Contact Data from this third-party partner to the extent permitted by the third-party partner, or as required for us to fulfill our legal obligations. We use this Personal Data as necessary to maintain the affiliate relationship and fulfill our obligations under applicable law, as well as for the general business and Commercial Purposes described further in our Privacy Policy.

### When you Contact us or Submit Personal Data to us

We collect and process Identity Data, Contact Data, Transaction Data, Usage Data, and User Content as necessary to address your request, fulfill the business purpose for which that data was provided, or for other related purposes. We process this Personal Data to respond to your request and to otherwise fulfill our contract or communicate with you, as appropriate. If you contact us to inquire about a product or Service, or for other similar purpose, we may use the Personal Data we collect for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### Warranty, Returns, and Repairs

If you have a warranty claim regarding a Corsair product you purchased, or if you submit a product for return/repair, we may collect additional Device/Network Data, as well as Identity Data, Contact Data, and Transaction Data in connection with the submission and processing of your claim. If you are entitled to a refund, we may collect Payment Data in order to process the refund transaction. We process this Personal Data as necessary to fulfill the transaction, and for our business purposes, described below.

### When you Interact with us in Person

We process your Contact Data and Identity Data when you interact with us in person, such as at an event, tradeshow, or conference. Additionally, in some cases, we may receive from organizers of events certain attendee data that includes your Identity Data or Contact Data. We will process this Personal Data to provide you with the information you request, in accordance with the rights we are granted by the organizers, including where appropriate or allowed by law, for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### Feedback and Surveys

We generally process Identity Data, Contact Data, Inference Data, and User Content collected in connection with customer surveys or questionnaires. We generally process this Personal Data as necessary to respond to customer requests/concerns, to create aggregate analytics regarding customer satisfaction, to improve our products, or to allow our third-party partners to communicate with customers. We may also store and analyze feedback related to our Service for our Commercial Purposes, including personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### Support and Professional Services

We collect and process Identity Data, Contact Data, Transaction Data, Usage Data, and in some cases, Device/Network Data, User Content (e.g. documentation or descriptions of issues) or Audio/Visual Data (e.g. recordings of support calls) when you contact us for support, or if we provide support and professional services to you as part of our Service. We use this Personal Data as necessary to provide support and professional services, to respond to your request, and to otherwise fulfill our contract with you, as appropriate. If you purchase these support and professional services from us, we will process information as set forth in the “When you make a Purchase or other Transaction through our Service” section above, including for our Commercial Purposes, including for personalization, to create consumer profiles, and for marketing purposes, as described below.

### Human Resources

If you are an applicant for a position at Corsair in California, the EEA, or the UK, Personal Data will be processed as set forth in the Corsair Human Resources Privacy Notice for California Residents.

BUSINESS AND COMMERCIAL PURPOSES OF PROCESSING
----------------------------------------------

In addition to the specific purposes described in this Privacy Policy, we may process any Personal Data we collect for certain internal business purposes and where necessary, as set forth below. If you would like more information about the legal basis for processing your Personal Data, please see the Supplemental Information below, or you can contact the Data Protection Officer at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com).

### Business Purposes

Service Provision & Contractual Obligations

We process Personal Data as necessary to process transactions, provide customer support, provide warranty service, and otherwise fulfill our contract with you.

Product and Service Improvement

We process Personal Data as necessary for our legitimate interests in understanding the use of and to improve our Service. For example, we process Personal Data as necessary to understand the performance of our Service, to improve our offerings, for internal purposes such as auditing or data analysis, to improve our software and devices, and for troubleshooting. For example, we may analyze access and control of device, configurations, notifications, or error reports submitted through our Service.

Security and Incident Detection

We may process Personal Data to improve the security of our Service, to identify and prevent crime, and prevent fraud. We may analyze network traffic, device patterns and characteristics, maintain and analyze logs and process similar Personal Data in connection with our information security activities.

Personalization

We process certain Personal Data as necessary in connection with our legitimate interest in personalizing our Service. For example, aspects of the Service may be customized to you so that it displays your name or reflects your preferences, to display content or features with which you have interacted in the past, or to display material that we think may be of interest to you based on your interactions with our Service. This processing may involve the creation and use of Inference Data relating to your preferences.

Aggregated/Anonymized data

We process Personal Data about our customers and users who use our Service in order to identify trends, such as to create aggregated or anonymized data about buying and spending habits, use of our Service, and other similar information (“**Aggregated Data**”). For example, we may process Aggregated Data to determine aggregate trends, response to various activities, games, and other aspects of our digital services. We may also retain and use this Aggregated Data in connection with the development of products or services. We may pass Aggregated Data to certain third parties to give them a better understanding of our business and to improve our Service. Aggregated Data will not contain information from which you may be personally identified.

Communicate with You

To respond, to communicate, reach out to you about your transactions or account, provide other relevant notifications or information, or request information or feedback. From time to time, we may use your Personal Data to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies, reports on device performance, notifications of upgrades, and flags for critical device security or performance issues.

Security, Safety, and Fraud Prevention

To protect individuals, employees, and Corsair brands, for loss prevention, and to prevent fraud, including to protect individuals, employees, and Corsair for the benefit of all our users.

Compliance Safety, and Public Interest

We may also process any Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, such as where you exercise your rights under data protection law and make requests, for the establishment and defense of legal claims, or where we must comply with our legal obligations, lawful requests from government or law enforcement officials, and as may be required to meet national security or law enforcement requirements or prevent illegal activity. We may also process data to protect the vital interests of individuals, or on certain public interest grounds, each to the extent allowed under applicable law.

### Commercial Purposes

Additionally, in some cases, we may use your data for certain commercial purposes, e.g. to help grow our business, to inform you of certain offers, to understand our customer, and in connection with other marketing or commercial purposes, as described below (“Commercial Purposes”).

Consumer Profiles

To understand our customers’ preferences and better recommend products and services that are personalized to our customers, we may create a consumer profile by linking together and analyzing Personal Data collected in the following contexts, in addition to those described in our Supplemental Privacy Notices:

* Account Registration
* When you make a Purchase or other Transaction through our Service
* When you Access or use our Service
* When you Use our Software or Certain Products
* Email and SMS Campaigns
* Cookies and Other Technologies
* Social Media Promoters
* When you Enter a Contest or other Promotion
* When you Contact us or Submit Personal Data to us
* When you Interact with us in Person
* Feedback and Surveys
* Support and Professional Services

We may also augment consumer profiles with Personal Data that we create (such as Inference Data) or that we receive from our Affiliates or third parties, which may include Personal Data such as information about which portions of our Service you have used previously, information about products you have purchased, devices and hardware that you use, and demographic data or other Inference Data.

We use consumer profiles for our legitimate interests in market research and statistical analysis in connection with the improvement of our Service. For example, we may analyze the Personal Data of people who have purchased certain products or services or who may be in the market for products of services. We may target our marketing to the new people we have identified in our database, for example by sending direct marketing emails. We may conduct the profiling and send direct marketing emails automatically. We may also use consumer profiles for other commercial purposes.

Marketing Communications

We (or if appropriate, certain third parties) may send you marketing and promotional communications if you sign up for such communications or purchase products or services from us. For example, we may process Contact Data and Identity Data when you opt-in to receive marketing communications via email or SMS text messaging. You may opt out of receiving these communications at any time.

Link Tracking/Read Receipts

In some email messages and to allow for secure software downloads and installations, Corsair sends to you, we provide a “click-through URL” that links you to content on the Sites. When you click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate server before arriving at the destination page on the Sites. We track this click-through to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure whether we are communicating with you effectively.

Targeted Advertising

We may engage in targeted advertising. This form of advertising includes various parties and service providers engaged in the processing of Personal Data in connection with advertising tailored to individual interests. These parties may be able to identify you across sites, devices, and over time. The parties that control the processing of Personal Data for targeted advertising purposes may create or leverage information derived from your profile and certain marketing communications. In some cases, these parties may also develop and assess aspects of a profile about you to determine whether you are a type of person to whom a company wants to advertise and to determine whether and how ads you see are effective. These third parties may augment your profile with demographic and other Inference Data derived from these observations, and may also track whether you view, interact with, or how often you have seen an ad, and whether you complete a purchase for a good or service you were shown in an advertisement.

Data Sales

Certain commercial processing involve “sales” of data as defined by applicable law. For example, we may “sell” certain Personal Data when we engage in certain social media marketing campaigns, conduct targeted online advertising, or sell or grant access to Personal Data to our marketing partners, sponsors, and other advertisers.

Lookalike Audiences

We may send marketing communications via social media or third-party platforms, including by creating custom marketing audiences on third-party websites (such as Facebook). Marketing communications may be personalized or customized based on your account profile.

YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS & CHOICES
-----------------------------

You may have certain rights and choices regarding the Personal Data we process. Please note these rights may vary based on the country or state where you reside, and our obligations under applicable law. Additional rights and disclosures for residents of the EEA, UK, Switzerland, California, Nevada, and other jurisdictions are described further below.

### Marketing Communications

You can withdraw your consent to receive marketing communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in an email or by submitting a request using the information below.

### Withdrawing Your Consent/Opt-Out/Opt-Out of Sales

Where we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent, you may change your mind and withdraw your consent at any time. The consequence of you withdrawing consent might be that we cannot perform certain services for you.

### Submission and Verification

To exercise your rights under applicable law, you may email us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com). If you decide to exercise your rights, to help protect the security of your Personal Data, you will be asked to verify your identity. There may be situations where we cannot grant your request, e.g. if Corsair is legally obligated to keep Personal Data to comply with applicable law. We may also decline to grant a request where our legitimate use of the data outweighs individual privacy concerns, e.g. in relation to anti-fraud and security purposes, or a request for deletion of an account that is being investigated for security concerns. We may also deny your privacy request if it jeopardizes the privacy of others, is frivolous or vexatious, and where applicable law allows the denial.

DATA RETENTION
--------------

We retain Personal Data for so long as it, in our discretion, is necessary to achieve the processing purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and in any event, for so long as is required by law or necessary to provide the Service. We will review retention periods periodically and may sometimes pseudonymize or anonymize data held for longer periods. We may also retain and use your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or for the period required or permitted by laws in applicable jurisdictions. Please note that some or all of the Personal Data we have collected may be required for the Service to function properly.

CORSAIR’S SHARING OF PERSONAL DATA
----------------------------------

Corsair may share Personal Data within our Affiliates and with service providers who act on our behalf, our partners, or others at your direction.

* **Service Providers**. Corsair may engage third parties to act as our service providers and perform certain tasks on our behalf, such as processing or storing data, delivering products to customers. Corsair’s service providers are obligated to handle Personal Data consistent with this Privacy Policy and according to our instructions.
* **Affiliates**. To streamline business operations and develop products and services that better meet the interests and needs of our customers and to inform our customers about relevant products and services, we may share your Personal Data with any of our current or future Affiliates.
* **Partners**. At times, Corsair may partner with third parties to provide services or other offerings. For example, Corsair offers financing in cooperation with partners who manage the extension of credit and financing offers. We may share Personal Data with these partners, and they may process Personal Data for their own purposes as a separate controller, or share certain Personal Data with Corsair, each as set forth in the applicable privacy policy.
* **Social Media/Advertisers**. To improve personalization, deliver more relevant advertisements to you and others, and develop better products and services, we may share certain Personal Data with third parties for marketing, advertising, or other commercial purposes, and we may allow third parties (such as Facebook and social media advertisers, ad exchanges, data management platforms, or ad servers) to operate on our Service and process data for targeted advertising. These transfers may be made for commercial purposes and in connection with data sales.
* **Data Aggregators**. In connection with our marketing operations, we may share certain Personal Data with data aggregators to help us better personalize our services, enrich Consumer Profiles and help ensure that you see advertisements that are more relevant to your interests.
* **Successors**. Any Personal Data may be processed in the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, liquidation, sale of all or a portion of our assets, joint venture, securities offering, bankruptcy, reorganization, liquidation, dissolution, or other transaction. For example, Personal Data may be part of the assets transferred, or may be disclosed (subject to confidentiality restrictions) during the due diligence process for a potential transaction.
* **Others**. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate. We may also disclose information about you where there is a lawful basis for doing so, if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or to protect our operations or users.

PROTECTION OF DATA AT CORSAIR
-----------------------------

We use administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your Personal Data, taking into account the nature of the Personal Data and the processing, and the threats posed. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate and reasonable in connection with the risk of processing your Personal Data.

While we take reasonable measures to protect Personal Data against loss, theft, and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. No Internet, email, or mobile application transmission is ever fully secure or error free. Email or other messages sent through the Service may not be secure.

TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA BETWEEN COUNTRIES
-------------------------------------------

We operate in and use service providers located in the United States. If you are located outside the U.S., your Personal Data may be transferred to the U.S. The U.S. does not provide the same legal protections guaranteed to Personal Data in the EEA, UK, and Switzerland. Accordingly, your Personal Data may be transferred to the U.S. pursuant to the Standard Contractual Clauses or other adequacy mechanisms or pursuant to exemptions provided under EU law. Contact us for additional information regarding the mechanisms to ensure adequate protection of data subject to these laws.

CHILDREN
--------

Except in limited cases described below or in our Supplemental Privacy Notices, our Service is not directed at users under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from minors unless we have the necessary consent from the child, parent, or guardian. If you have reason to believe that we may have accidentally received Personal Data from a minor, please contact us immediately at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com).

Designated portions of our Service, such as Gamer Sensei, may be used by children under the age of majority with the consent of Parents/Guardians. As Parents/Guardians, if you consent to your child’s use of the Service, we may collect and process certain additional Personal Data. Where we handle the Personal Data of children under the age of majority in the applicable jurisdiction, Parents/Guardians may have certain rights in their child’s Personal Data under applicable law. For example, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act gives Parents/Guardians the right to access, correct, and delete their child’s Personal Data (subject to limited exceptions). Additional information regarding Parents/Guardians’ consent, supplemental processing of Personal Data, and the rights of Parents/Guardians in relation to the Gamer Sensei service is available in the Gamer Sensei Privacy Supplement.

PRIVACY QUESTIONS
-----------------

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you can contact us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com) .The data controller of your Personal Data is Corsair Memory, Inc. which is registered in the state of Delaware.

CHANGES AND UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
-----------------------------------------

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically, especially before you provide any information. This Privacy Policy was made effective on the date indicated above.

HOW TO CONTACT US
-----------------

**CORSAIR MEMORY, Inc.**  
115 N. McCarthy Boulevard, Milpitas, CA 95035  

SUPPLEMENTAL INFORMATION
------------------------

### SUPPLEMENTAL INFORMATION FOR USERS IN THE EEA/UK/SWITZERLAND

### Legal Bases for Processing Your Information (For Users in EEA/UK)

Performance of a contract

The use of your Personal Data may be necessary to perform the agreement you have with us to provide products and services, e.g. to ship your products you have ordered, open and maintain your user accounts, or process your request.

Legitimate interests

We may use your Personal Data for our legitimate interests. For example, we rely on our legitimate interest to administer, analyze and improve our content, to operate our business including through the use of service providers and subcontractors (who may have access to your data – see further under the section Corsair’s Sharing of Personal Data), to send you notifications about our services, for archiving, recordkeeping, statistical and analytical purposes, and to use your Personal Data for administrative, fraud detection, audit, training, security, or legal purposes. See the Purposes of Processing section above for more information regarding these processes.

Consent

You are free to withdraw any consent you may have provided, at any time, subject to the [Your Privacy Rights and Choices](#your-privacy-rights--choices) section and the preceding [Legal Bases for Processing Your Information](#legal-bases-for-processing-your-information-for-users-in-eeauk) in this Section.

Compliance with legal obligations

We may use your Personal Data to comply with legal obligations to which we are subject, including to comply with legal processes.

Performance of a task carried out in the public interest

We may use your Personal Data to perform a task in the public interest or that is in the vital interests of an individual.

### EEA/UK/Swiss Privacy Rights

Users based in the EEA/UK/Switzerland (“User”) have the following legal rights with respect to their information:

* The right to require Corsair to confirm whether or not their information is being processed, the purpose of any such processing, the recipients of any information that has been disclosed, the period for which their information is to be stored, and whether any automated decision-making processes are used in relation to their information;
* The right to require Corsair to rectify inaccurate information without undue delay;
* The right to request the erasure of their information. Subject to certain conditions, Corsair may be required to erase the information in response to such request where:
    * the information is no longer necessary in relation to the purpose for which it was collected, such as where a User chooses to terminate his or her use of the Service;
    * the processing of the information is based on the User’s consent (and the other circumstances described in the Legal Bases for Processing Your Information and Corsair’s Sharing of Personal Data sections above no longer apply), if the User withdraws his or her consent; or
    * the User objects to the processing of his or her information and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing.
* Where Corsair has disclosed the information of an EEA/UK user to a third party and the user requests the erasure or rectification of the data, Corsair will take all reasonable steps to inform the third party of such request.
* The right to restrict Corsair from processing User information in certain circumstances, such as where the accuracy of that information is disputed or an objection has been raised (see below). In such circumstances, Corsair will only process that information with the express consent of the User, or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims, or for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person, or for reasons of important public interest;
* User’s right to receive their information from Corsair in a structured, commonly-used and machine-readable format;
* User’s right to object to the processing of their information by Corsair where:
    * Corsair has relied on the “legitimate interest” basis for processing that information, in which case we will immediately stop processing the User’s information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds which override the interests, rights, and freedoms of the User; or
    * the information is used for direct marketing purposes, in which case we will immediately stop processing the User’s information for such purposes; and
* The right to lodge a complaint with the data protection supervisory authority of the EU member state where the User resides or the data protection supervisory authority in the UK (where applicable).

The above legal rights are subject to various conditions and exceptions, including where the data is used for statistical or scientific research purposes, and the exercise of the right would prevent such purposes from being attained or would seriously impair their attainment.

SUPPLEMENTAL INFORMATION FOR NEVADA RESIDENTS
---------------------------------------------

The Nevada Revised Statutes (NRS 603A.300 et seq.) permit a Nevada consumer to direct an operator of an Internet website or online service to refrain from making any sale of any covered information the operator has collected or will collect about that consumer. You may submit a request pursuant to this directive by emailing us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com). We will provide further information about how we verify the authenticity of the request and your identity.

SUPPLEMENTAL INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
-------------------------------------------------

California residents have the following rights. You will not need to create an account to exercise your rights. To exercise one of these rights, please provide a verifiable consumer request by emailing us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com).

### Your California Privacy Rights

Right to Delete

You have the right to delete certain Personal Data that we hold about you, subject to exceptions under applicable law.

Direct Marketing

You may request a list of Personal Data we have disclosed about you to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.

Right to Know

You may request that, for Personal Data that we have collected in the preceding 12 months, we disclose, free of charge (unless your requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive) (1) the categories of Personal Data we have collected about you, or that we have sold, or disclosed for a Commercial Purpose; (2) the categories of sources from which your Personal Data was collected; (3) the business or Commercial Purpose for which we collected or sold your Personal Data; (4) the categories of third parties to whom we have sold your Personal Data or disclosed it for a business purpose; and (5) the specific pieces of Personal Data we have collected about you.

Do Not Sell My Personal Information

You may direct us, at any time, not to sell your Personal Data. We may sell personal information as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). Under the CCPA, “sell” means sell, rent, release, disclose, disseminate, make available, transfer, or otherwise communicate orally, in writing, or by electronic or other means a consumer’s personal information by the business to another business or a third party for monetary or other valuable consideration. The law contains exceptions to this definition which may limit how we respond to your direction.

Nondiscrimination

We may not discriminate against you because you exercised any of your rights under the CCPA, including, but not limited to, by: (A) denying goods or services to you; (B) charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties; (C) providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you; or (D) suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

However, nothing prohibits us from charging you a different price or rate, or from providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you, if that difference is reasonably related to the value provided to us by your data.

We may offer financial incentives, including payments to you as compensation, for the collection of personal information, the sale of personal information, the retention of personal information, or the deletion of personal information. We may also offer a different price, rate, level, or quality of goods or services to you if that price or difference is directly related to the value provided to us by your data.

### Submission of Requests

To exercise this right to opt out, you may email us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com).

### Verification of Requests

Before we can fulfill the requests to know and delete your personal information , we must verify your identity. If you have a password-protected account with us, we can verify your identity through our existing authentication procedures for your account. However, we will require you to re-authenticate yourself before we can disclose or delete any of your personal information.

If you do not have a password-protected account with us, we will require you to provide us with two types of information to verify your identity. This information may include your name, telephone number, email address, or home address, as well as supplemental information, such as purchase data or other unique information in your account. We may also require you to provide a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose personal information is the subject of the request. We will match this information to the Personal Data we maintain.

You can also authorize another person, called an agent, to exercise your rights on your behalf. You must provide the authorized agent written and signed permission to act on your behalf. We may deny requests to opt out from an authorized agent who does not submit proof that he or she has been authorized to act on your behalf. Furthermore, we may require you to verify your identity directly with us. We may also require you to directly confirm with us that you have provided the authorized agent permission to submit a request on your behalf. An authorized agent can make a request on your behalf by emailing us at [data.controller@corsair.com](mailto:data.controller@corsair.com).

### Right to Know Disclosure

The charts below summarize how we process specific categories of Personal Data. Please see the corresponding definitions/headings above for more information regarding each category of Personal Data, the purposes of processing, and categories of recipients.

| Categories of personal information collected in last 12 months | Purposes for which personal information will be used |
| --- | --- |
| Identity Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction; Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Email and SMS Campaigns; Cookies and Other Technologies; Social Media Promoters; Contest/Promotions; Affiliate Relationships; Contact us/Submissions; Warranty, Returns, and Repairs; In Person Interactions; Feedback and Surveys; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Device/Network Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction; Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Email and SMS Campaigns; Cookies and Other Technologies; Social Media Promoters; Contest/Promotions; Affiliate Relationships; Contact us/Submissions; Warranty, Returns, and Repairs; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Contact Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction; Access or use of our Service; Email and SMS Campaigns; Social Media Promoters; Contest/Promotions; Affiliate Relationships; Contact us/Submissions; Warranty, Returns, and Repairs; In Person Interactions; Feedback and Surveys; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Payment Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction; Warranty, Returns, and Repairs; Business Purposes |
| Transaction Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction; Cookies and Other Technologies; Social Media Promoters; Contest/Promotions; Contact us/Submissions; Warranty, Returns, and Repairs; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Audio/Visual Data | Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Usage Data | Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Cookies and Other Technologies; Contact us/Submissions; Feedback and Surveys; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Inference Data | Account Registration; Purchase or other Transaction ; Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Email and SMS Campaigns; Cookies and Other Technologies; Contest/Promotions; Feedback and Surveys; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Location Data | Account Registration; Access or use of our Service; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |
| Government ID Data | Social Media Promoters; Contest/Promotions; Business Purposes |
| User Content | Access or use of our Service; Use of our Software or Certain Products; Contest/Promotions; Contact us/Submissions; Feedback and Surveys; Support and Professional Services; Business Purposes; Commercial Purposes |

| Categories of personal information that we have sold in last 12 months | Categories of third parties to whom the information was sold |
| --- | --- |
| Identity Data | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |
| Device/ NetworkData | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |
| Contact Data | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |
| Transaction Data | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |
| Usage Data | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |
| Inference Data | Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators |

| Categories of personal information that we have disclosed for business/commercial purposes in last 12 months | Categories of third parties to whom the information was disclosed |
| --- | --- |
| Identity Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Device/Network Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Contact Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Payment Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Successors; Others |
| Transaction Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Audio/Visual Data. | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Successors; Others |
| Usage Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Inference Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Location Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Social Media/Advertisers; Data Aggregators; Successors; Others |
| Government ID Data | Service Providers; Affiliates; Successors; Others |
| User Content | Service Providers; Affiliates; Partners; Successors; Others |

OTHER SUPPLEMENTAL PRIVACY NOTICES
----------------------------------

© 2024 Drop

Company

[About Drop Studio](https://drop.com/studio)[Student Discount](https://drop.com/student-discount)[Privacy Policy](https://drop.com/privacy)[Terms of Use](https://drop.com/terms)Cookie Settings

Drop Refurbished

Drop Rewards

Get $5 for every 500 points you earn! [Learn more](https://drop.com/help/rewardsprogram)

Drop Keyboard Club

Collaborate With Us

Support

Follow Drop

© 2024 Drop
